# Vladyslav Makoda

#### Software engineer

I have been developing in this field for about 4 years, and now I am looking for a stable job, looking for various types of vacancies, mostly part-time, office/home work format. I'm interested in software developer, web developer, QA, Data Analyst positions.

✓ vlad.makoda@gmail.com



+421950202069



Košice, Slovakia

github.com/Lyten1



linkedin.com/in/vladyslav-makoda-6b3043276

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Computer Science**

#### Technical University of Košice

09/2022 - Present

Kosice

- 3rd year
- · Heroes of Might&Magic is a browser-based multiplayer analogue of the famous game that combines component programming technologies. Nominated by "Best of games 2024"
- Baguvix final game for selection in the first half of the year, nomina ted by "Best of games 2022"

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Founder & Programing teacher TukeUp

09/2022 - Present

Kosice

- Explaining information
- Performing tasks
- Managing process

#### Software engineer

#### Olos

01/2024 - Present

Kosice

A team which develops custom software and participates in hackathons

- Java, Spring
- Python
- Databases
- Data analytics

#### **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

• Financia - my project for convenient reporting of finances, expenses and profits, data visualization, multinational platform with tracking of different currencies simultaneously

03/2024 - Present

Java, MVC, Repositories, PostgreSQL, CurrencyAPI

• Zhlobo - analogy of the Glovo delivery app Tech

10/2023 - 02/2024

OOP, Java, PostgreSQL, Spring Boot, Repositories, MVC, CRUD

· MCalculator - Specialised calculator for calculating vehicle clearance costs, which is now used for commercial purposes

09/2020 - 12/2020

C++, OOP, InternetParser, SQLite

#### ORGANIZATIONS

AWS user group Kosice

06/2024 - Present

Member

#### CERTIFICATES

Basics of software testing

07/2024 - Present

QA/QC, Testing algorithms, Testing rules

#### LANGUAGES

English Slovak Ukrainian